{
    "subject": "resource/Sinclair_Vehicles",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Sinclair Vehicles Ltd was a company formed in March 1983 by Sir Clive Sinclair as a focus for his work in the field of electric vehicles. The initial investment was \u00a38.6m, which came from the proceeds of the sale of some of Sir Clive's shares in Sinclair Research. Barrie Wills, formerly of the DeLorean Motor Company, was appointed as managing director.The first (and only) Sinclair Vehicles production model was the single-seater Sinclair C5, launched on 10 January 1985.",
    "human_readable": "The comment about Sinclair Vehicles Ltd is that it was a company formed in March 1983 by Sir Clive Sinclair as a focus for his work in the field of electric vehicles. The initial investment was \u00a38.6m, which came from the proceeds of the sale of some of Sir Clive's shares in Sinclair Research. Barrie Wills, formerly of the DeLorean Motor Company, was appointed as managing director. The first (and only) Sinclair Vehicles production model was the single-seater Sinclair C5, launched on 10 January 1985.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9222363233566284,
            "question": "What was the initial investment for Sinclair Vehicles Ltd?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.910161018371582,
            "question": "What was the name of the managing director appointed for Sinclair Vehicles Ltd?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9033091068267822,
            "question": "What field did Sinclair Vehicles Ltd focus on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8745087385177612,
            "question": "When was Sinclair Vehicles Ltd formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8168145418167114,
            "question": "Who founded Sinclair Vehicles Ltd?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7854791879653931,
            "question": "From where did the funding for Sinclair Vehicles Ltd originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7819685935974121,
            "question": "Who was the former employee of DeLorean Motor Company appointed as managing director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.717515230178833,
            "question": "Did Sinclair Vehicles Ltd produce any other models besides the Sinclair C5?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5945059657096863,
            "question": "What type of vehicle was the Sinclair C5?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.574626088142395,
            "question": "When was the Sinclair C5 launched?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment about Sinclair Vehicles Ltd is that it was a company formed in March 1983 by Sir Clive Sinclair as a focus for his work in the field of electric vehicles. The initial investment was \u00a38.6m, which came from the proceeds of the sale of some of Sir Clive's shares in Sinclair Research. Barrie Wills, formerly of the DeLorean Motor Company, was appointed as managing director. The first (and only) Sinclair Vehicles production model was the single-seater Sinclair C5, launched on 10 January 1985.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5331_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of vehicle was the Sinclair C5?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5331_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Sinclair Vehicles Ltd produce any other models besides the Sinclair C5?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5331_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the former employee of DeLorean Motor Company appointed as managing director?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5331_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5331_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5331_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5331_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5331_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5331_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5331_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5331_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5331_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5331_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5331_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text describes Sinclair Vehicles Ltd and its founding by Sir Clive Sinclair in March 1983 with an initial investment of \u00a38.6m from the sale of shares in Sinclair Research. It also mentions Barrie Wills as the managing director and the launch of the C5 on January 10, 1985.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that \"The comment about Sinclair Vehicles Ltd is that it was a company formed in March 1983 by Sir Clive Sinclair as a focus for his work in the field of electric vehicles. The initial investment was \u00a38.6m, which came from the proceeds of the sale of some of Sir Clive's shares in Sinclair Research. Barrie Wills, formerly of the DeLorean Motor Company, was appointed as managing director. The first (and only) Sinclair Vehicles production model was the single-seater Sinclair C5, launched on 10 January 1985.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context information fully supports the statement about Sinclair Vehicles Ltd. It mentions that the company was formed in March 1983 by Sir Clive Sinclair for his work in electric vehicles, with an initial investment of \u00a38.6 million from the sale of shares in Sinclair Research, and Barrie Wills as managing director. Additionally, it confirms that the first (and only) production model was the single-seater Sinclair C5, launched on 10 January 1985."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}